import {Question} from './question-helper';

export let QUESTIONS: Question[] = [
  {
    question: 'My preferred weapon of choice in conflict:',
    answers: ['Compassion', 'Axe', 'Sword', 'Negotiation']
  },
  {
    question: 'My favourite sport:',
    answers: ['Tai Chi', 'MMA', 'Fencing', 'Archery']
  },
  {
    question: 'The quality which best describes me:',
    answers: ['Passionate', 'Intrepid', 'Noble', 'Stoic']
  },
  {
    question: 'My favourite music genre:',
    answers: ['New Age', 'Heavy Metal', 'Rock & Roll', 'Classical']
  },
  {
    question: 'The colour which best reflects my response to a challenge:',
    answers: ['', '', '', '']
  },
  {
    question: 'My strategy when someone initiates an argument:',
    answers: ['Deference', 'Assault', 'Engage', 'Depart']
  },
  {
    question: 'When making a critical decision, I usually follow',
    answers: ['My heart', 'An impulse', 'The leader', 'My intuition']
  },
  {
    question: 'The Superhero power I wish I could have:',
    answers: ['Healing', 'Invincibility', 'Clairvoyance', 'Mentifery']
  },
  {
    question: 'The consequence to someone caught stealing should be:',
    answers: ['Community service', 'Corporeal punishment', 'Monetary fine', 'Counselling and education']
  },
  {
    question: 'If I am outnumbered in a confrontation and face almost certain defeat, I would',
    answers: ['Surrender', 'Fight until death',
      'Strategically out-maneuver my enemy, to avoid direct conflict', 'Retreat, and reformulate my strategy']
  },
  {
    question: 'If I witness a stranger being attacked, and in dire need of assistance, I would ...',
    answers: ['Call for help', 'Slay the assailants',
      'Intimidate the assailants into retreat', 'Distract the assailants, so the victim may flee']
  },
  {
    question: '_______ mightier than the sword',
      answers: ['The heart is', 'I am', 'The shield is', 'The pen is']
  },
  {
    question: 'The archetype which best represents my personality:',
    answers: ['Caregiver', 'Rebel', 'Hero', 'Sage']
  },
  {
    question: 'My favourite movie genre:',
    answers: ['Romance', 'Horror', 'Action', 'Mystery']
  },
  {
    question: 'The personality trait I need to improve:',
    answers: ['Insecure', 'Volatile', 'Narcissistic', 'Arrogant']
  },
  {
    question: 'The critical element essential to success in my life:',
    answers: ['Faith', 'Strength', 'Respect', 'Honour']
  }
];
